(Leonard:)No, we just made out.
(Mandy:)Oh. Well, good for me.
(Mandy:)So what can I do for you?
(Leonard:)Uh, okay, well, um,
I got married recently.
Oh, congratulations!
(Mandy:)To Sheldon?
(chuckles)
(Leonard:)Never gets old.
(Leonard:)No, no, to a girl.
(Leonard:)Anyway, I told her what happened
between you and me,
(Leonard:)and she's concerned about us
seeing each other at work.
(Mandy:)It was just a kiss.
Why would you even tell her?
(Leonard:)Because I didn't want there
to be any secrets between us.
(Mandy:)Is that really the reason?
(Leonard:)What else would it be?
(Penny:)I don't know.
(Mandy:)Sounds like you're trying
to sabotage the relationship.
(Leonard:)No, I don't think so.
(Leonard:)Although,
Penny did say exactly that.
(Mandy:)Okay, well, that's something
to think about.
(Leonard:)You know, on some level,
I've always believed
(Leonard:)that I don't deserve
a woman like her.
(Mandy:)Oh, you're gonna
think about that right here?
(Leonard:)I mean, she's really beautiful.